

Eric Beltran

www.ericbeltran.com • emedia@ericbeltran.com • 541.515.0357 • Portland, OR

PROFILE

Multimedia design graduate with strong creativity skills and expertise in a variety of design applications. Excellent communicator, organizer, and problem solver. Quick learner, with a demonstrated ability to meet deadlines and work well in fast-paced or demanding environments.

EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL CONSULTANT

University of Oregon, 2005-07 / Center for Educational Technologies

- · Provided campus-wide technical support for all educational software and hardware needs.
- Assisted faculty with extensive variety of multimedia projects, examples including web production, video editing, network management, disk cloning and digital imaging support.
- Demonstrated strong ability to handle multiple projects and establish appropriate priorities.

LAB MANAGER

University of Oregon, 2004-06 / Yamada Language Center

• Hired, trained, and managed small staff responsible for upkeep and maintenance of twenty plus computer terminals and laptop checkout in multi-platform computer lab.

MEDIA INSTRUCTOR

University of Oregon, 2005-07 / Faculty Media Workshops

• Instructed faculty in educational and emerging technologies geared toward classroom implementation during summer intensive media workshops.

MULTIMEDIA DESIGNER

University of Oregon, 2004-07 / University of Oregon

 Designed posters, programs, T-shirts and created online promotional videos for the University's 'Foreign Language and International Studies Day' celebration, averaging one-thousand participants annually.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF OREGON

B.A. Multimedia Design, B.A. International Studies, June 2007

- 3.78 GPA for multimedia major (4.0 scale)
- · Deans List, 2007
- Study abroad term, Rosario, Argentina, Fall 2006

PROGRAMS

Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Acrobat Professional, Flash, Dreamweaver, Fireworks

Final Cut Pro, DVD Studio Pro, Soundtrack Pro, Compressor, Motion

Autodesk Combustion, Maya, Cinema 3D XL

Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint

Actionscript 2.0, HTML, Mac and Windows troubleshooting, and networking.

AWARDS

UO DIGITAL ART EXPLOSION FESTIVAL

• Animation piece selected for competitive media festival, 2007.

LAVERNE KRAUSE GALLERY

Graphic work displayed during one week media show, 'Creative Mention' award, 2007.

DOWNTOWN INITIATIVE FOR THE VISUAL ARTS FILM FESTIVAL

Video piece selected for entry into competitive summer festival, 2006.